Blockchain is basically a "shared ledger" that can be used to record any transactions and also makes it nearly impossible to change past transactions. As data is sent or received, it is synchronized across the blockchain, which is cost effective, saves time, and energy. All of the transactions are also very secure and authenticated. 

*Ask mama on projects to work for on blockchain*


Gupta, Manav. Blockchain for Dummies. 3rd ed., John Wiley & Sons, Inc., 2018.
