Conclusion:

The data was collected using human subjects and Coolors.co. The 3 parameters were the RGB values of each color swatch and the category was determined by taking the majority vote from the categories given. Then a grid search was used to find the best possible combination of hidden layer(s) and nodes. 

The best test score was 69% that used 6 nodes in one hidden layer. When graphing the test scores of different nodes and layers, an increase-then-decrease pattern was noticed. Figure 1 shows how the different parameters affected the categories. Figures 2 and 3 show the test scores of the hidden layers tested in the grid search. 

This project would have worked better if there was only one set of colors used, instead of four. There were some overlapping parameters for the four color sets which created outliers and mixing. Because of the mixed data points the neural network could not properly identify a specific color from the 10 different colors. If there was only one color set used then identifying the color would have easier.