Introduction:
6(5) paragraphs


1st attention getter/purpose
Identifying colors can cause bickering, debates, break friendships, divide countries, and start world wars. Many times these things happen, but maybe a neural network trained to identify colors can help settle disputes on a small scale. 


2nd-4th background research
People can see the same color differently because physiological differences in their eyes. The cells in the retina called photoreceptors are sensitive to the RGB colors. Different people have photoreceptors that are sensitive at different wavelengths of a color. So one person may view a color as red while another may view it as a red-orange. So everyone is seeing the same color but their brains process them differently and so a person's perspective of that color may differ from another's.[1]

The RGB color system interprets how much red, green, and blue is present in a given color. The scale of the system is done in the decimal system and ranges from 0 to 255 where 0 is the lowest concentration and 255 is the highest concentration. That means that there are 16581375 possible colors and if the RGB values of two colors are close enough, they could look exactly the same.[2]

A neural network is a type of machine learning that has many layers consisting of nodes. Data moves in one direction from one layer to another, interconnected by the nodes from those layers. The layers and nodes are adjusted to get the most pleasant result. In this way the neural network is trained to categorize a set of untrained data and show its accuracy. 

5th goal
The goal is to make a neural network which will produce a test result higher the 50%. It is also to discover patterns in test scores as the number of nodes and hidden layers changes to possibly predict a variation of hidden layers and nodes to get a higher result.


6th summary of procedures
After data was collected, a neural network was created to train and test the data. A grid search was used to determine the best combination of hidden layers and nodes to produce the best result. The data was also cross validated. 



1. “What If Two People Call a Color the Same Name but Their Eyes See Different Colors? Is It Proven That That's Not Possible?” UCSB Science Line, National Science Foundation and UCSB, 11 Apr. 2004, http://scienceline.ucsb.edu/getkey.php?key=719.
2. “Understanding Hexadecimal Colors Is Simple.” Pluralsight, Pluralsight, 19 Jan. 2015, https://www.pluralsight.com/blog/tutorials/understanding-hexadecimal-colors-simple.
3. Hardesty, Larry. “Explained: Neural Networks.” MIT News, MIT, 14 Apr. 2017, http://news.mit.edu/2017/explained-neural-networks-deep-learning-0414.