Procedure:
The language used is Python version 3.7.3. The libraries numpy version 1.16.4, sci-kit version 0.21.2, pandas version 0.24.2, matplotlib version 3.1.0, and seaborn version 0.9.0 were also installed. 

The data was collected from Coolors.co. Random colors were generated with the website and information such as RGB. A survey was sent out to human participants to determine the categories of the colors. The category with the majority of votes was determined to be the category of that color. 

The different red, green, blue values of each color were the parameters. The 12 outcomes were pink, salmon, orange, green, blue, turquoise, yellow, chartruese, purple, periwinkle, white, off white, and gray.   

The data was cross-validated by using a grid search to test many hidden layers and the best set of hidden layers was chosen. 



cse citation sytle
Number bibliography
	inparagragth citations just use superscript of the number


Cross-validation with  …………..

